<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Nicolas Blogs</title><link>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Nicolas Blogs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><managingEditor>190563@llinstitute.com (Nicolas Arias)</managingEditor><webMaster>190563@llinstitute.com (Nicolas Arias)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Incredible Advances In Artificial Intelligence (AI) And The Best Project Sophia.</title><link>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/second-post/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>190563@llinstitute.com (Nicolas Arias)</author><guid>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/second-post/</guid><description>Sophia has artificial intelligence software that allows her to maintain eye contact with people, from which she can retain information and even recognize their faces, as well as being able to trace the human personality: she can have a conversation, explain jokes, etc. Is that not amazing? Sophia is a humanoid (gynoid) robot developed by the Hong Kong-based company Hanson Robotics. It has been designed to learn, adapt to and work with human behavior successfully.</description></item><item><title>E-sports as a measure of mass entertainment</title><link>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>190563@llinstitute.com (Nicolas Arias)</author><guid>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid><description>Today, E-sports are for some more entertaining than any traditional sport and, according to a study, it has been proven that young people, both women and men, consume more these E-sports than any other traditional sport. Before we get into the impact of E-sports in real life, I will first focus on what they are.
What are E-sports. E-sports or electronic sports are a novelty in the field of video games.</description></item></channel></rss>