<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Nicolas' Blogs</title><link>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Nicolas' Blogs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><managingEditor>190563@llinstitute.com (Nicolas Arias)</managingEditor><webMaster>190563@llinstitute.com (Nicolas Arias)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tecnological mask for covid by XIAOMI</title><link>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/5post/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>190563@llinstitute.com (Nicolas Arias)</author><guid>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/5post/</guid><description>###XIAOMI PRESENTS ITS ELECTRIC ANTI-GERMA MASK THAT YOU WILL CHARGE BY USB
It goes without saying how useful these masks have become in our country, which have been sold out in many pharmacies despite the fact that experts warn that they are of little use, unless we have the Covid-19 disease and, then yes, we can avoid infecting others. In any case, in China, which are experts in carrying out this type of objects even if there are no health emergencies due to coronavirus, they have solutions of all kinds, such as this model.</description></item><item><title>Massively revolutionary technological inventions in 2020</title><link>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/4post/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>190563@llinstitute.com (Nicolas Arias)</author><guid>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/4post/</guid><description>Advances in technology are happening at breakneck speed and 2020 is expected to be the year of the so-called great technological leap. Industries are rapidly preparing to enter a new era where robots, the Internet of Things (IoT) and other trends in innovation will take center stage today. Every year new technologies come to our hands; When it comes time to renew the computer, mobile phone or other devices, or when we undergo a medical procedure, we are always benefiting from the latest advances that have reached the market.</description></item><item><title>Functions that you may not know and are innovative of the apple watch.</title><link>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/3post/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>190563@llinstitute.com (Nicolas Arias)</author><guid>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/3post/</guid><description>When the Apple Watch appeared in 2015, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t just a new product - it was Apple&amp;rsquo;s entry into wearable products, a market it had previously avoided. Unfortunately, without an interface tradition to lean on, it was difficult for Apple to achieve the same levels of intuitive usability that it had achieved on the Mac, iPhone, and iPad.
Obviously, Apple wasn&amp;rsquo;t going to give up, so the company forged a new design language.</description></item><item><title>The Incredible Advances In Artificial Intelligence (AI) And The Best Project Sophia.</title><link>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/second-post/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>190563@llinstitute.com (Nicolas Arias)</author><guid>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/second-post/</guid><description>Sophia has artificial intelligence software that allows her to maintain eye contact with people, from which she can retain information and even recognize their faces, as well as being able to trace the human personality: she can have a conversation, explain jokes, etc. Is that not amazing? Sophia is a humanoid (gynoid) robot developed by the Hong Kong-based company Hanson Robotics.
It has been designed to learn, adapt to and work with human behavior successfully.</description></item><item><title>E-sports as a measure of mass entertainment</title><link>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>190563@llinstitute.com (Nicolas Arias)</author><guid>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid><description>Today, E-sports are for some more entertaining than any traditional sport and, according to a study, it has been proven that young people, both women and men, consume more these E-sports than any other traditional sport. Before we get into the impact of E-sports in real life, I will first focus on what they are.
What are E-sports. E-sports or electronic sports are a novelty in the field of video games.</description></item></channel></rss>