<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Nicolas' Blogs</title><link>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Nicolas' Blogs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><managingEditor>190563@llinstitute.com (Nicolas Arias)</managingEditor><webMaster>190563@llinstitute.com (Nicolas Arias)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The most innovative military projects.</title><link>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/15post/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>190563@llinstitute.com (Nicolas Arias)</author><guid>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/15post/</guid><description>The technological advances we have seen in 2019 never cease to amaze us. We have seen creative applications of artificial intelligence, blockchain, robotics or the internet of things to the most diverse sectors, without exception. Technology advances by leaps and bounds in all kinds of areas, but there is one field where innovation tends to be one step ahead: the military.
Concern about the cyber component of wars 4.0 is not trivial and the investment that governments make in cybersecurity grows as awareness grows about the importance of protecting themselves in cyberspace.</description></item><item><title>artificial skin that makes you invisible.</title><link>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/14post/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>190563@llinstitute.com (Nicolas Arias)</author><guid>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/14post/</guid><description>Invisibility has been the subject of science fiction and fantasy literature since time immemorial, but in reality, the practical options to achieve it did not exist. The closest we could see was a Canadian startup that developed a shield in 2019 that made whatever was behind it difficult to see, but it was far from what we know for true invisibility and, even more, portable.
Now, a team of scientists from Seoul National University in South Korea has developed a type of camouflage mask that uses triggering heating and cooling mechanisms to mimic the colors of the surrounding environment.</description></item><item><title>Floating hoverboard.</title><link>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/13post/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>190563@llinstitute.com (Nicolas Arias)</author><guid>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/13post/</guid><description>You may already know about self-driving cars and hovercrafts. But what about hoverboards? Picture it: You&amp;rsquo;re flying down the sidewalk on an object that looks like a skateboard without wheels! You turn a corner, swerve around other people, and get home from school in record time, without ever touching the ground!
Does this sound like science fiction? Think again! Hoverboards are already a reality.
But how do hoverboards work?
The &amp;ldquo;hoverboards&amp;rdquo; some of your friends are already riding are self-balancing scooters.</description></item><item><title>Robotic Surgery.</title><link>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/12post/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>190563@llinstitute.com (Nicolas Arias)</author><guid>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/12post/</guid><description>About robotic surgery Robotic surgery was quickly adopted in hospitals in the United States and Europe as a treatment for a wide range of conditions.
The most widely used clinical robotic surgical system features a camera arm and mechanical arms, and surgical instruments mounted on them. The surgeon controls the arms while seated at a computer console near the operating table. The console provides the surgeon with a high definition magnified three-dimensional view of the surgical site.</description></item><item><title>Lakes In London To Visit.</title><link>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/10post/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>190563@llinstitute.com (Nicolas Arias)</author><guid>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/10post/</guid><description>London is blessed with beautiful bodies of water, so take a peek at these lovely lakes. The next time somebody tells you that London is all concrete and no nature, tut loudly and send them a link to this article. Or, better still, take them to one of these beautiful lakes within the city. That’ll show them. Quite literally.
Art
Victoria Park Boasting 86.18 hectares of open space, two boating lakes (one is for model boats only), a splash pool, and a Chinese pagoda, Victoria Park was voted the people’s favourite park back in 2014.</description></item><item><title>Smart houses, the new era of our way to live.</title><link>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/9post/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>190563@llinstitute.com (Nicolas Arias)</author><guid>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/9post/</guid><description>Smart homes are those in which electrical, gas or water installations are remotely monitored and controlled from an electronic device. Usually it is usually the mobile or the computer. In this post we tell you how they work and all the benefits they can bring.
Advantages of smart homes The automation of homes, thanks to telemetry and home automation, is serving to have custom houses, adjusted to the particular needs of each individual.</description></item><item><title>Art and History.</title><link>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/7post/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>190563@llinstitute.com (Nicolas Arias)</author><guid>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/7post/</guid><description>Art.
Art
Art (from Latin ars) is the concept that encompasses all creations made by humans to express a sensitive vision about the world, whether real or imaginary. Through plastic, linguistic or sound resources, art allows to express ideas, emotions, perceptions and sensations.
History indicates that, with the appearance of Homo Sapiens, art had a ritual and magical-religious function, which changed over time. However, the definition of art varies according to the time and the culture.</description></item><item><title>Wingsuit powered by BMW.</title><link>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/11post/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>190563@llinstitute.com (Nicolas Arias)</author><guid>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/11post/</guid><description>In collaboration with BMW, Peter Salzman, pioneer of the Irish parachute saint, designed an electric wingsuit called a &amp;ldquo;wingsuit&amp;rdquo; that powers his flight and allows him to reach speeds of 300 kilometers per hour. The new suit is powered by a chest-mounted rig and produces a total power of 15 kW. This amount is divided into two 7.5 kW carbon impellers that rotate at a speed of 25,000 RPM and produce a thrust of up to five minutes.</description></item><item><title>The 5 Best VR Companies in the World</title><link>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/6post/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>190563@llinstitute.com (Nicolas Arias)</author><guid>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/6post/</guid><description>We know that gaming is evolving constantly. With the way things are going, it seems that the controller may become an artifact of gaming, much like the joystick from the 1970s and 1980s. How could such a thing happen? Controllers are essential. Well, if these virtual reality companies have anything to say about it, our bodies will be the only controllers we need.
This extends to further aspects, like apps and video technologies.</description></item><item><title>Tecnological mask for covid by XIAOMI</title><link>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/5post/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>190563@llinstitute.com (Nicolas Arias)</author><guid>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/5post/</guid><description>XIAOMI PRESENTS ITS ELECTRIC ANTI-GERMA MASK THAT YOU WILL CHARGE BY USB It goes without saying how useful these masks have become in our country, which have been sold out in many pharmacies despite the fact that experts warn that they are of little use, unless we have the Covid-19 disease and, then yes, we can avoid infecting others. In any case, in China, which are experts in carrying out this type of objects even if there are no health emergencies due to coronavirus, they have solutions of all kinds, such as this model.</description></item><item><title>Massively revolutionary technological inventions in 2020</title><link>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/4post/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>190563@llinstitute.com (Nicolas Arias)</author><guid>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/4post/</guid><description>Advances in technology are happening at breakneck speed and 2020 is expected to be the year of the so-called great technological leap. Industries are rapidly preparing to enter a new era where robots, the Internet of Things (IoT) and other trends in innovation will take center stage today. Every year new technologies come to our hands; When it comes time to renew the computer, mobile phone or other devices, or when we undergo a medical procedure, we are always benefiting from the latest advances that have reached the market.</description></item><item><title>Functions that you may not know and are innovative of the apple watch.</title><link>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/3post/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>190563@llinstitute.com (Nicolas Arias)</author><guid>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/3post/</guid><description>When the Apple Watch appeared in 2015, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t just a new product - it was Apple&amp;rsquo;s entry into wearable products, a market it had previously avoided. Unfortunately, without an interface tradition to lean on, it was difficult for Apple to achieve the same levels of intuitive usability that it had achieved on the Mac, iPhone, and iPad.
Obviously, Apple wasn&amp;rsquo;t going to give up, so the company forged a new design language.</description></item><item><title>The Incredible Advances In Artificial Intelligence (AI) And The Best Project Sophia.</title><link>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/second-post/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>190563@llinstitute.com (Nicolas Arias)</author><guid>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/second-post/</guid><description>Sophia has artificial intelligence software that allows her to maintain eye contact with people, from which she can retain information and even recognize their faces, as well as being able to trace the human personality: she can have a conversation, explain jokes, etc. Is that not amazing? Sophia is a humanoid (gynoid) robot developed by the Hong Kong-based company Hanson Robotics.
It has been designed to learn, adapt to and work with human behavior successfully.</description></item><item><title>E-sports as a measure of mass entertainment</title><link>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>190563@llinstitute.com (Nicolas Arias)</author><guid>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid><description>Today, E-sports are for some more entertaining than any traditional sport and, according to a study, it has been proven that young people, both women and men, consume more these E-sports than any other traditional sport. Before we get into the impact of E-sports in real life, I will first focus on what they are.
What are E-sports. E-sports or electronic sports are a novelty in the field of video games.</description></item><item><title>Tesla, the new Era cars.</title><link>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/8post/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>190563@llinstitute.com (Nicolas Arias)</author><guid>https://nikoarias.github.io/posts/8post/</guid><description>Tesla Model 3 can change the world. The second half of the 19th century and the beginning of the 20th were characterized by the discovery and introduction of electricity in modern societies. Those were the times of Thomas Edison, Alexander Graham Bell, and Nikola Tesla. Electricity was the new fad, but for various reasons the fad did not thrive in the auto industry.
The first automobile with an internal combustion engine was invented in 1807 by François Isaac de Rivaz, but it was not until 1886 that the German engineer Karl Benz perfected it enough to be useful and for everyday use.</description></item></channel></rss>